ugamezone.com 2019-08-27

# Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our site. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

01

## COOKIES POLICY

UGameZone ("we" or "us") use cookies and other similar technologies in the operation of this website. 

A cookie is a piece of information that a website puts on your computer so it can remember something about you or your device at a later date. We use cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website (including when you browse other third party websites). This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse this website. We also use cookies and similar technologies to show you more personalised advertising, including adverts on other websites. By using our website, you agree to our use of cookies. This policy explains what cookies, including third party cookies, we use on our website, and how you can refuse or withdraw your consent to cookies. You can find more information about cookies at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and [www.youronlinechoices.eu](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). 

The cookies on our website are either set by us or by third party partners and fall into the following categories: 

  * __

### FIRST PARTY SESSION MANAGEMENT

These are typically required by us to make sure you can move freely from one page to another and so you can access and use certain services within the site. Normally these cookies only last while your browser is open and are deleted when it is closed. Some may need to remain for longer than the duration of your visit (session) or longer. 

Cookie name | Description | Duration  
---|---|---  
played | Used by our platform to log the games you played | 30 days  
  * __

### PERFORMANCE

We want to ensure we provide a good experience. These cookies (which are set by third parties providing services to us) allow us to monitor how visitors use our website. These cookies provides us with anonymous statistics on how many people visit the website, where they have come from and the pages they visit so that we can continue to develop and improve the website and our services. They also help us understand the effectiveness of our advertising. 

Third party | Description  
---|---  
Google Analytics | Collects statistical information about how you use the site so that we can improve the site  
<https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>  
  * __

### FUNCTIONALITY

These cookies allow you to set and store preferences for the website, such as when you login to post comments or where you are offered the option to customise elements of the layout or content of the website. These cookies may also help us to monitor, debug and optimise the performance of the website. 

Third party | Description  
---|---  
Google | [Types of cookies used by Google](https://policies.google.com/technologies/types?hl=en) [https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies](https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies?hl=en)  
Facebook | Social media integration. <https://facebook.com/policy.php>  
Twitter | Social media integration. <https://dev.twitter.com/web/overview/privacy>  
  * __

### INTEREST-BASED ADVERTISING

These cookies allow third parties to identify what you might find interesting, allowing a more personalised and relevant selection of advertisements to be displayed when you browse the internet. They normally won't just be from us, but build an overall, but anonymous, picture of individuals' preferences based how they have browsed the internet, in order to deliver more relevant advertising. You may see interest-based advertising on our website, but also on third party websites using information collected about your browsing activity on our website. 

Third party | Description  
---|---  
Google | Tracks performance of advertising campaigns. <https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads>  
Doubleclick | Our partners with third party technologies including Doubleclick to deliver efficient media buying. <https://policies.google.com/privacy>  
  * __

### REFUSING OR WITHDRAWING YOUR CONSENT TO THE USE OF COOKIES

You may refuse to accept cookies by altering the settings on your internet browser. For more information about how to do this, look at your browser 'help' section or visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and [www.youronlinechoices.eu](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). 

Please note that if you adjust your internet browser settings to refuse the setting of cookies, you may not be able to access or use fully certain parts or functionality of our website. 

  * __

### UPDATES TO THIS POLICY

So that we can offer you the best possible online experience, new services using cookies may be added to our website from time to time. We aim to keep the cookies information provided here as accurate as possible and use all reasonable efforts to regularly review and update the details. When we update these details we will post changes on this page so please check back frequently. 

02

## USE OF FACEBOOK AND GOOGLE SOCIAL PLUGINS

UGAMEZONE.COM ("UGAMEZONE") uses social plugins ("plugins") of the social networks Facebook and Google on its website from facebook.com, which is operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, United States ("Facebook") and google.com, which is operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, California, 94043, United States ("Google+1"). The plugins are marked with their logos: Facebook and Google+1. If the customer visits a web page on UGAMEZONE, which contains such a plugin, the browser builds up a direct link to the Facebook or Google servers. The contents of the plugin is from Facebook and Google directly to the browser of the customer and integrated into this website. 

By integrating these plugins Facebook and Google receive information that the customer has visited UGAMEZONE. If the customer is logged into Facebook or Google, these companies can assign the visit of UGAMEZONE to his or her Facebook/Google account. When the customer interacts with the plugins, for example, the "Like" button, "+1 Button" or add a comment, the corresponding information from the client's browser is sent directly to Facebook or Google and stored there. Purpose and scope of data collection and further processing and use of data through Facebook or Google are related to the settings of the customer to protect his privacy, refer to the privacy policies of Facebook or Google.

03

## LINKS

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

04

## ADVERTISERS

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process and are collected by our ad companies, we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies: Google. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)

05

## INFORMATION USAGE

We will only use your personally identifiable information as described below, unless you have specifically consented to another type of use, either at the time the personally identifiable information is collected from you or through some other form of consent from you:

  * __We will use personally identifiable information to provide you with the specific services that you have requested;
  * __We will use your personally identifiable information to respond to questions that you send to us;
  * __We will use your personally identifiable information to send you emails from time to time, such as newsletters and notices about our promotions;
  * __We may disclose personally identifiable information as required by law or legal process; and
  * __We may disclose personally identifiable information to investigate suspected fraud, harassment or other violations of any law, rule or regulation, or the terms or policies for the Web site.

06

## OPT OUT/CORRECTIONS

Upon your request, we will

  * __correct or update your personal information;
  * __stop sending emails to your email address; and/or
  * __disable your account to prevent any future purchases through that account.

You can make these requests at the customer information section, or by telephoning, or emailing your request to UGAMEZONE’s Customer Support department at [support@ugamezone.com](mailto:support@ugamezone.com).

Please do not email your credit card number or other sensitive information.
